hi sterling Allen here at the
extraordinary technology 2011 it is July
29th and yesterday
Vernon Roth gave a very interesting
presentation on hydroxy Browns gas
HHO technology various things for those
similar types of processes and talked
about transportation developments toward
the end and that really got my interest
say everything he was saying was very
fascinating it's been a friend of mine
for quite a few years and we go back in
our connections so it's an honor for me
today to do a recording of him I'm going
to be holding the camera where we got a
side room here so we can get some quiet
and just can be asking some questions
about these technologies and the
opportunities that are involved with
these technologies so you can read an
interview or this interview online will
be posted at PBS ENCOM and a date close
to this one we'll be posting this to
YouTube and however many segments it
takes so here's the interview with
Thurman Roth
all right Vernon maybe you can just
really quick tell us about your website
and just a thumbnail sketch of a
biography of you know what you do and
where you're coming from
okay well my first website is each and
techcom and that is my family site too
to educate and sell our our products
that we developed by researching ancient
technology and reproducing our world
there's different types of elements
different creams that we produced from
ancient formulas and they have healing
effects and beneficial effects for the
bodies so check out ancient tech that's
Tek com another website and I actually
just took control of that again it was
very difficult to change anything or
post anything it's called alchemical
hydrogen and that's where a lot of the
information that I presented yesterday
and the information I'll be talking
about well it's actually going to be
posted and I'll have videos up there and
such as well now that I have you know
control of that to to post up there and
that's the subject that has me most
intrigued obviously there's a lot of
things we could talk about you've been
involved in the hydroxy research for
years and I have been chasing that dream
along with a lot of other people and
have been working in concert with other
people as well and had been giving
presentations at this Tesla tech
conference for years but the alchemical
hydroxy or hydrogen is fascinating if I
could recap it briefly you were talking
about taking the hydrogen oxygen in the
electrolysis process and that somehow
the in in your setup at least you've
been able to replicate the elements that
are in the water in solution whether
they're minerals or even chemical and
they actually replicated 10 13 times in
a given process so you could actually
like make copies of whatever's in the
water using this process did I summarize
that pretty well yes you're surprised
very well that's what the research is is
showing now that's and it's it's kind of
fantastical but that's what we're
actually experiencing is this
replication of minerals and
multiplication I should tell you too
that you're not the only one that says
that I've heard other people describe
that phenomena that the stuff that was
in the Joe cell and actually I should
mention that as the Joe cell set up
using the hydroxy in the Joe cell where
this shows up some research Peter
Stevens I think mentioned that and
others I would say that there at least
three other people who have described
independently that phenomenon so you
were the first person to say that
yesterday that's and that's one of the
reason why I'm not just rolling my eyes
saying I'll wait and see is now that
I've heard it enough there's something
to this you know where there's smoke
there's fire kind of thing and another
thing that's exciting about what you're
doing is you're willing to share this
quite openly with people to help them do
the same thing so let's first talk about
the kind of the lay of the land maybe
take five minutes and describe how you
do this and what's going on what you
have observed that kind of a snippet
from your presentation yesterday at the
Tesla tech conference
well I start with an essential hydrogen
device that I followed the ballboys
method of using of using parallel
stainless steel plates and I didn't put
electricity and certain ratios into the
into those plates and I don't use it for
this process I don't use sodium
hydroxide or potassium hydroxide as the
catalyst I rely on the natural
conductivities of different elements and
the water that I work with to be the
conductor of energy and so it's not as
efficient as a conventional hydrolysis
so but we're not really looking for huge
volumes of gas here what we're looking
for is the subtle energy is that that's
that's my that's my my passionate field
research is the subtle etheric energy
that we could start to imprint a pattern
on and allow it to manifest in the
physical reality and that's really what
this comes down to is is is finding
these swirling vortexes of ether putting
a pattern into it and finding the energy
to make it a physical reality and that's
where I believe that that's where the
elements are coming from and part of
that is the huge portion of that is the
separation of the oxygen hydrogen
allowing that to recombine so I know
that there are there people that
experience transmutation of elements in
in the hydrogen gas flame but now we're
starting to actually see that in the
hydrogen chamber as well so that's
what's really exciting my process uses
stainless steel plates and we have to
vary the the current and voltage ratios
a little bit but we can talk about that
might eat a of the the the process a
little bit later I use the stainless
steel plates and put energy across it
and what happens is elements that are
present already in the in the liquid
start to
condense and drop out at the bottom of
the device so it's very important that
the stainless steel plates or not are
not locked in in a solid case but
actually have room for for liquid to
flow around and the elements will fall
down and because that's where they
accumulated then you can draw them off
as they over time as they develop so
that's the basic principle and then I of
course I'm very much safety oriented so
I'm not using a giant mason jar or
something like that I've blown up too
many cells and to uh to play around with
plexiglass I use half inch to 3/4 inch
thick PVC pipe and stainless steel
plates to hold everything together and
so it's very it's a very safe device so
that's what I use in particular and then
actually instead of using regular
electric power from the wall or from
from a generator
I actually just hook it up to a solar
panel and then 300 Watts right yeah 300
watts will give you about will give you
a significant amount of will give you a
significant amount of gas production my
first initial experiment I was getting I
was getting twenty liters an hour off of
a $45 solar panel from from Harbor
Freight and it was only generating in
the neighborhood of a hundred and a
hundred watts or so so it was kind of
exciting
to actually see elements and they
developed a usable byproduct of hydrogen
gas that we can burn later just coming
from the Sun with it with
the minimum of expenses really exciting
so describe the process of of you've got
something in solution a mineral that is
being duplicated
well the my see I started I've actually
done this in another way I do it all the
time in another way based off of an
ancient technology that we discovered
and the the process is you have a stream
of hydrogen and a stream of oxygen gas
and if you have a crystalline matrix of
whatever element that you are
reproducing to form if then you have
etheric energy an accumulator that you
direct the energy through the
crystalline matrix pattern the ether and
that flows into the hydrogen and the
oxygen then you have a spark there to
combine that hydrogen and oxygen and
because you've just patterned the energy
that is there the hydrogen oxygen formed
into the element that you're after this
kind of flies in the face of
conventional physics and kind of ok it
flies in the face of conventional
physics but you know we're gonna
discover that we don't really know a
whole lot I mean even even this last
year of conventional physics was turned
on its head by a couple of discoveries
when they when they learned about the
interaction of light and magnetism and
they said well they admitted in the
scientific journals they said we don't
understand why this happens all of our
mathematics say that we should be
getting X number of energy but we're
getting orders of magnitude higher than
that just with the interaction of light
magnets so conventional physics and and
our
of reality it's not complete and anybody
who says this is just a little little
arrogant there so we have to understand
that there's more to know than what we
know right now and we have to be open to
the information as it comes in so and I
actually challenge everybody that sees
this to to experiment with this and find
out if I'm right find out if and and
find out of the other people that are
that are reproducing elements and and
seeing the transmutation are actually
correct because I would like to know and
I want to I want the proof out there and
I want people playing with it because as
we did the experiments someday
conventional science will catch up and
this will become commonplace in a
hundred years from now or maybe less
than that let's hope they'll actually
use the use processes or this
understanding to to make the things that
we need and we won't have lack that we
won't have to we won't have mining as we
understand it now we will actually use
energy to create matter and we're
talking Star Trek technology here but
that's the future and the people that
wrote that were visionaries so that's my
that's my goal that's what I'd like to
see happen just conceptually this is a
variation of the 3d printing that
they're talking about where you put in
something into an auto cad machine and
it'll actually print out a 3d rendering
of a device that you can they use it's a
practical device yes and the difference
being that you're not printing something
from a set of plans you're actually on a
nano or molecular level you're
reproducing a given substrate that's
there so you're making a copy of dole
you're making a copy of some expensive
minerals some some expensive molecule it
doesn't have to be mineral right
actually the way I knew that I was
actually reproducing something was I was
doing an experiment with an alchemical
fluid that I make that takes quite a
long time to make and quite an is quite
an intensive process and when I put that
into the Machine and started finding
that the fluid was actually coming but
that more of the fluid was coming out
the other end than I started with
and it was stronger and better than what
I started with that's when I knew that I
wasn't just reproducing and that's a
single element or a single mineral I was
actually reproducing a complex it was
actually quite a complex reproduction
and was not just was not just limited to
a single atom template so that was very
very exciting for me to discover that
because a it means that I have a whole
lot less work to do in certain areas
because it's very difficult to produce
that but also that gives me a whole new
only responsibility as we work well
that's that's psycho-spiritual
observation that we go into here at the
technology world but it's very exciting
it's very exciting to know that we don't
just have to we don't just reproduce a
single element we can actually reproduce
complex elements using energy you
describes a number of ten to thirteen
times the amount of the original
substrate being reproduced in this
process do you want to describe how you
came up with that number
well that was done by some friends that
were doing Joe cell research and they
had the conventional stainless steel
tubes they put in a mineral toddy
Clark's minerals organum minerals
there's different types of minerals they
put in a mineral toddy into this this
this Joe cell device which is a very
powerful etheric energy accumulator as
is generating hydrogen and they were
able to through a series of boiling or
generating hydrogen and oxygen
recombining it that's and starting the
process all over again they were able to
actually multiply the mineral content by
13 times i sterling Allen here at the
extraordinary technology 2011 it is July
29th and yesterday
Vernon Roth gave a very interesting
presentation on hydroxy Browns gas hecho
technology various names for those
similar types of processes and talked
about transferring for many segments it
takes so here's the interview with
German Roth
alright Vernon maybe you can just really
quick tell us about your website and
just a thumbnail sketch of a biography
of you know what you do and where you're
coming from
okay well my first website is ancient
tech comm and that is my family site to
to educated and sell our our products
that we developed by researching ancient
technology and reproducing our world
there's different types of elements
different creams the bathroom here so we
can get some quiet and just gonna be
asking some questions about these
technologies and the opportunities that
are involved with these technologies so
you can read an interview or this
interview online will be posted at PE SN
dot-com and a date close to this one
we'll be posting this to YouTube and
navigation developments toward the end
and that really got my interest so
everything he was saying was very
fascinating it's been a friend of mine
for quite a few years and we go back in
our connections so it's an honor for me
today to do a recording of him I'm going
to be holding the camera where we got us